Spirit of God => B-PERSON
garden of Eden => B-LOCATION
garden => B-LOCATION
Holy Spirit => B-PERSON
I AM => B-PERSON
Mount Sinai => B-LOCATION
LORD => B-PERSON
Lord => B-PERSON
Lord your God => B-PERSON
LORD God => B-PERSON
beginning => B-TIME
seasons => B-TIME
years => B-TIME
night => B-TIME
day => B-TIME
evening => B-TIME
morning => B-TIME
God => B-PERSON
I => B-PERSON
Cain => B-PERSON
Abel => B-PERSON
Adam => B-PERSON
Eve => B-PERSON
Euphrates => B-LOCATION
Enoch => B-PERSON
Methushael => B-PERSON
Tigris => B-LOCATION
Nod => B-GPE
Irad => B-PERSON
Mehujael => B-PERSON
Lamech => B-PERSON
Adah => B-PERSON
Zillah => B-PERSON
Eden => B-GPE
Assyria => B-GPE
Havilah => B-GPE
Pishon => B-LOCATION
Cush => B-PERSON
Spirit => B-PERSON
Gihon => B-LOCATION
Jabal => B-GPE
Jubal => B-GPE
Naamah => B-PERSON
Seth => B-PERSON
Enosh => B-PERSON
Kenan => B-PERSON
Jared => B-PERSON
Mahalalel => B-PERSON
Methuselah => B-PERSON
Noah => B-PERSON
Shem => B-PERSON
Ham => B-PERSON
Japheth => B-PERSON
Nephilim => B-PERSON
Noahs => B-PERSON
Ararat => B-LOCATION
Canaan => B-GPE
Gomer => B-PERSON
Magog => B-GPE
Madai => B-PERSON
Javan => B-PERSON
Tubal => B-PERSON
Meshech => B-PERSON
Tiras => B-PERSON
Ashkenaz => B-PERSON
Riphath => B-PERSON
Togarmah => B-PERSON
Elishah => B-PERSON
Tarshish => B-GPE
Kittim => B-PERSON
Dodanim => B-PERSON
Mizraim => B-PERSON
Put => O
Seba => B-PERSON
Sabtah => B-PERSON
Raamah => B-PERSON
Sabteca => B-PERSON
Sheba => B-PERSON
Dedan => B-PERSON
Nimrod => B-PERSON
Babel => B-GPE
Erech => B-GPE
Accad => B-GPE
Calneh => B-GPE
Shinar => B-GPE
Nineveh => B-GPE
Abraham => B-PERSON
Sarah => B-PERSON
Calah => B-GPE
Resen => B-GPE
Ludim => B-PERSON
Anamim => B-PERSON
Lehabim => B-PERSON
Naphtuhim => B-PERSON
Pathrusim => B-PERSON
Casluhim => B-GPE
Philistines => B-ORGANIZATION
Caphtorim => B-GPE
Sidon => B-GPE
Heth => B-PERSON
Jebusite => B-ORGANIZATION
Amorite => B-ORGANIZATION
Girgashite => B-ORGANIZATION
Hivite => B-ORGANIZATION
Arkite => B-ORGANIZATION
Sinite => B-ORGANIZATION
Arvadite => B-ORGANIZATION
Zemarite => B-ORGANIZATION
Hamathite => B-ORGANIZATION
Canaanite => B-ORGANIZATION
Gerar => B-GPE
Gaza => B-GPE
Sodom => B-GPE
Gomorrah => B-GPE
Admah => B-GPE
Zeboiim => B-GPE
Lasha => B-GPE
Elam => B-PERSON
Asshur => B-PERSON
Arpachshad => B-PERSON
Lud => B-PERSON
Hul => B-PERSON
Gether => B-PERSON
Mash => B-PERSON
Shelah => B-PERSON
Eber => B-PERSON
Peleg => B-PERSON
Joktan => B-PERSON
Almodad => B-PERSON
Nahor => B-PERSON
Abram => B-PERSON
Terah => B-PERSON
Haran => B-GPE
Sarai => B-PERSON
Milcah => B-PERSON
Abrams => B-PERSON
Haran => B-GPE
Lot => B-PERSON
Bethel => B-GPE
Egypt => B-GPE
Zoar => B-GPE
Mamre => B-GPE
Egyptian => B-PERSON
Hagar => B-PERSON
Ishmael => B-PERSON
Isaac => B-PERSON
Abimelech => B-PERSON
Abrahams => B-PERSON
Beersheba => B-GPE
Rebekah => B-PERSO
Rebekahs => B-PERSON
Laban => B-PERSON
Labans => B-PERSON
Aramean => B-ORGANIZATION
Jacob => B-PERSON
Esau => B-PERSON
Rachel => B-PERSON
Rachels => B-PERSON
Leah => B-PERSON
Zilpah => B-PERSON
Bilhah => B-PERSON
Jacobs => B-PERSON
Joseph => B-PERSON
Shechem => B-PERSON
Be => O
Behold => O
Me => B-PERSON
Please => O
O => O
Us => B-PERSON
Aram => B-GPE
Come => B-O
Jordan => B-LOCATION
Hebron => B-GPE
Chedorlaomer => B-PERSON
Him => B-PERSON
Return => O
No => O
Ephron => B-PERSON
Drink => O
Bethuel => B-GPE
How => O
Gilead => B-GPE
Hamor => B-PERSON
See => O
Egyptians => B-GPE
Pharaoh => B-PERSON
Pharaohs => B-PERSON
Pharaoh => B-PERSON
Perizzite => B-ORGANIZATION
Sea => O
Hebrew => B-ORGANIZATION
Dan => B-PERSON
Bring => O
Hittite => B-ORGANIZATION
Almighty => O
Your => O
A => O
Take => O
Machpelah => B-GPE
Canaanites => B-ORGANIZATION
Midian => B-GPE
Hanoch => B-PERSON
Hittite => B-ORGANIZATION
Esaus => B-PERSON
Edom => B-GPE
Gods => B-PERSON
Reuben => B-PERSON
Simeon => B-PERSON
Levi => B-PERSON
Leahs => B-PERSON
Seir => B-LOCATION
Succoth => B-GPE
Dinah => B-PERSON
Ephrath => B-GPE
Benjamin => B-PERSON
Judah => B-PERSON
Naphtali => B-PERSON
Asher => B-PERSON
Anah => B-PERSON
Zibeon => B-PERSON
Eliphaz => B-PERSON
Oholibamah => B-PERSON
Jeush => B-PERSON
Jalam => B-PERSON
Korah => B-PERSON
Teman => B-ORGANIZATION
Kenaz => B-PERSON
Amalek => B-PERSON
Eliphaz => B-PERSON
Reuel => B-PERSON
Zerah => B-PERSON
Zibeon => B-PERSON
Dishon => B-PERSON
Shaul => B-PERSON
Josephs => B-PERSON
Sheol => B-LOCATION
Onan => B-PERSON
Tamar => B-PERSON
Judah => B-PERSON
Perez => B-PERSON
LORDS => B-PERSON
Josephs => B-PERSON
Hebrew => B-ORGANIZATION
Hebrews => B-ORGANIZATION
Pharaohs => B-PERSON
Nile => B-LOCATION
Asenath => B-PERSON
Potiphera => B-PERSON
Ephraim => B-PERSON
Go => O
Egyptians => B-ORGANIZATION
Thus => O
Goshen => B-GPE
Say => O
Reuben => B-PERSON
Hezron => B-PERSON
Simeon => B-PERSON
Levi => B-PERSON
Merari => B-PERSON
Manasseh => B-PERSON
Dan => B-PERSON
Ephraims => B-PERSON
Moses => B-PERSON
Zipporah => B-PERSON
AM => O
Stretch => O
Jethro => B-PERSON
Aaron => B-PERSON
Nadab => B-PERSON
Abihu => B-PERSON
Eleazar => B-PERSON
Ithamar => B-PERSON
Aarons => B-PERSON
Tomorrow => O
Rise => O
Red => O
Unleavened => O
Bread => O
Aarons => B-PERSON
Marah => B-LOCATION
Sinai => B-LOCATION
My => O
Joshua => B-PERSON
Mount => B-LOCATION
Bezalel => B-PERSON
Uri => B-PERSON
Hur => B-PERSON
Oholiab => B-PERSON
Ahisamach => B-PERSON
Whoever => O
\nAnd => O
b'And => O
Myself => O
Speak => O
Mine => O
Molech => B-PERSON
b'Again => O
Himself => O
Negev => B-LOCATION
Kadesh => B-GPE
Amalekites => B-ORGANIZATION
Amorites => B-ORGANIZATION
Eshcol => B-LOCATION
Stand => O
Moab => B-PERSON
Paran => B-GPE
Zebulun => B-PERSON
Pallu => B-PERSON
Gershon => B-PERSON
Kohath => B-PERSON
Issachar => B-PERSON
Gad => B-PERSON
Uzziel => B-PERSON
Amminadab => B-PERSON
Amorites => B-ORGANIZATION
Nun => B-PERSON
Levites => B-ORGANIZATION
Shedeur => B-PERSON
Zurishaddai => B-PERSON
Nahshon => B-PERSON
Zuar => B-PERSON
Helon => B-PERSON
Ammihud => B-PERSON
Pedahzur => B-PERSON
Gideoni => B-PERSON
Ammishaddai => B-PERSON
Ochran => B-PERSON
Deuel => B-PERSON
Enan => B-PERSON
Gershonites => B-ORGANIZATION
Kohathites => B-ORGANIZATION
Nazirite => B-ORGANIZATION
Midianite => B-ORGANIZATION
Miriam => B-PERSON
Caleb => B-PERSON
Jephunneh => B-PERSON
Dathan => B-PERSON
Abiram => B-PERSON
Eliab => B-PERSON
Hor => I-GEO
Arnon => B-LOCATION
Sihon => B-GPE
Heshbon => B-GPE
Beor => B-PERSON
Balaam => B-PERSON
Balak => B-PERSON
Zippor => B-PERSON
Balak => B-PERSON
Peor => B-LOCATION
Bela => B-GPE
Salt => O
Rephaim => B-ORGANIZATION
GOD => B-PERSON
Ammon => B-PERSON
Beriah => B-PERSON
Rameses => B-PERSON
Machir => B-PERSON
Horeb => B-LOCATION
Amram => B-PERSON
Passover => O
Etham => B-GPE
Elim => B-GPE
Sin => O
Rephidim => B-LOCATION
Urim => O
Zin => B-LOCATION
Oboth => B-LOCATION
Ar => B-GPE
Pisgah => B-LOCATION
Jazer => B-GPE
Bashan => B-GPE
Reubenites => B-ORGANIZATION
Hoglah => B-PERSON
Tirzah => B-PERSON
Zelophehad => B-PERSON
Abarim => B-LOCATION
Og => B-PERSON
Jericho => B-GPE
Arabah => B-LOCATION
Anakim => B-ORGANIZATION
Argob => B-LOCATION
Arise => O
Hivites => B-ORGANIZATION
Jebusites => B-ORGANIZATION
Hittites => B-ORGANIZATION
nations => B-GPE
nation => B-GPE
wilderness => B-LOCATION
earth => B-LOCATION
Will => O
Israel => B-GPE
Lebanon => B-GPE
heavens => B-LOCATION
heaven => B-LOCATION
Again => O
And => O
Israels => B-GPE
Levite => B-ORGANIZATION
Abib => O
Weeks => O
Levitical => B-ORGANIZATION
Amen => O
Ebal => bB-LOCATION
Ai => B-GPE
High => O
Make => O
Carmi => B-PERSON
Consecrate => O
Booths => O
Meribah => B-LOCATION
Great => O
Rahab => B-PERSON
Achan => B-PERSON
Goiim => B-GPE
Kenizzite => B-ORGANIZATION
Hormah => B-GPE
Arad => B-GPE
Dibon => B-GPE
Medeba => B-GPE
Edrei => B-GPE
Hepher => B-GPE
Aroer => B-GPE
Libnah => B-GPE
Chinnereth => B-GPE
Jabbok => B-LOCATION
Hermon => B-LOCATION
Aroer => B-GPE
Gadites => B-ORGANIZATION
Geshurites => B-ORGANIZATION
Maacathites => B-ORGANIZATION
Gerizim => B-LOCATION
Gilgal => B-GPE
Gibeon => B-GPE
Jarmuth => B-GPE
Lachish => B-GPE
Debir => B-GPE
Eglon => B-PERSON
Jerusalem => B-GPE
Makkedah => B-GPE
Hazor => B-GPE
Dinahs => B-PERSON
Paddan-aram => B-GPE
Basemath => B-PERSON
Edomites => b-ORGANIZATION
Horites => b-ORGANIZATION
Timnah => B-GPE
Anak => B-PERSON
Mahlah => B-PERSON
Rabbah => B-GPE
Achor => B-LOCATION
Gezer => B-GPE
Tappuah => B-GPE
Perizzites => B-ORGANIZATION
Luz => B-GPE
Bethlehem => B-GPE
Shimron => B-GPE
Simeonites => B-ORGANIZATION
Rekem => B-PERSON
Beeroth => B-GPE
Achshaph => B-GPE
Arba => B-PERSON
Shiloh => B-GPE
Ramah => B-GPE
Rehob => B-GPE
Jahaz => B-GPE
Kedesh => B-GPE
Moabites => B-ORGANIZATION
Mesopotamia => B-GPE
Ahiman => B-PERSON
Talmai => B-PERSON
Akrabbim => B-LOCATION
Ashtaroth => B-PERSON
Megiddo => B-LOCATION
Ekron => B-GPE
Ehud => B-PERSON
Moreh => B-LOCATION
Penuel => B-GPE
Deborah => B-PERSON
Ishmaelites => B-ORGANIZATION
Midianites => B-ORGANIZATION
Alas => O
Baal => B-PERSON
Kenite => B-ORGANIZATION
Ophrah => B-GPE
Sisera => B-PERSON
Barak => B-PERSON
Abinoam => B-PERSON
Tabor => B-LOCATION
Kishon => B-LOCATION
Jael => B-PERSON
Gideon => B-PERSON
Asherah => B-PERSON
Joash => B-PERSON
Oreb => B-PERSON
Zeeb => B-PERSON
Zebah => B-PERSON
Zalmunna => B-PERSON
Where => O
Abiezrites => B-ORGANIZATION
Jerubbaal => B-PERSON
Ebed => B-PERSON
Zebul => B-PERSON
Gaal => B-PERSON
Jephthah => B-PERSON
Up => O
Eshtaol => B-GPE
Zorah => B-GPE
Gileadite => B-ORGANIZATION
Manoah => B-PERSON
Samson => B-PERSON
Lehi => B-GPE
Delilah => B-PERSON
Micah => B-PERSON
shekel => B-MONEY
shekels => B-MONEY
coin => B-MONEY
coins => B-MONEY
talents => B-MONEY
silver => B-MONEY
gold => B-MONEY
Messiah => B-PERSON
David => B-PERSON
Babylon => B-GPE
Mary => B-PERSON
Jesus => B-PERSON
THE => O
SHALL => O
AND => O
THEY => O
Judea => B-GPE
YOU => B-PERSON
LAND => B-LOCATION
OF => O
THE => O
Herod => B-PERSON
Child => B-PERSON
IN => O
WERE => O
Galilee => B-GPE
John => B-PERSON
NOT => O
WILL => O
Get => O
FOR => O
Pharisees => B-ORGANIZATION
Son => B-PERSON
YOUR => O
Follow => O
Father => B-PERSON
Gentiles => B-ORGANIZATION
Man => B-PERSON
HIS => O
NO => O
OUT => O
MY => O
OUT => O
CHILDREN => B-PERSON
TO => O
John the Baptist => B-PERSON
HIS => B-PERSON
Sadducees => B-ORGANIZATION
ON => O
BUT => O
AGAINST => O
Satan => B-PERSON
HIM => B-PERSON
Capernaum => B-GPE
WHO => O
THEM => O
Simon Peter => B-PERSON
Simon => B-PERSON
Peter => B-PERSON
James => B-PERSON
Zebedee => B-PERSON
Prophets => B-PERSON
WIFE => B-PERSON
AWAY => O
GIVE => O
HER => B-PERSON
LOVE => O
Law => O
FROM => O
ME => B-PERSON
HE => B-PERSON
Teacher => B-PERSON
Judas Iscariot => B-PERSON
Judas => B-PERSON
MY => O
Elijah => B-PERSON
Sabbath => B-Time
HEART => O
THEIR => O
EYES => O
WITH => O
AS => O
IS => O
Jesus Christ => B-PERSON
Christ => B-PERSON
Tell => O
Friend => B-PERSON
Mount of Olives => B-LOCATION
Scriptures => O
ALL => O
SITTING => O
LIGHT => O
Andrew => B-PERSON
NEIGHBOR => B-PERSON
Beelzebul => B-PERSON
Tyre => B-GPE
HEAR => O
Nazareth => B-GPE
Rabbi => B-PERSON
Master => B-PERSON
Barabbas => B-PERSON
Pontius Pilate => B-PERSON
Pilate => B-PERSON
Nazarene => B-ORGANIZATION
WILDERNESS => B-LOCATION
READY => O
STRAIGHT => O
EVERY => O
THAT => O
STONE => O
GENTILES => B-ORGANIZATION
THOSE => O
ADULTERY => O
FALSE => O
SET => O
MOTHER => B-PERSON
HAVE => O
Bethsaida => B-GPE
UPON => O
SEE => O
Herodias => B-PERSON
Philip => B-PERSON
OR => O
Isaiah => B-PERSON
Seven => O
ANDTHE => O
ONE => O
YOURSELF => O
NAME => O
CALLED => O
Bethany => B-GPE
IT => O
Caesars => B-PERSON
HAND => O
CLOUDS => O
Caiaphas => B-PERSON
Hail => O
Crucify => O
Most => O
DO => O
DOES => O
QUENCHED => O
Zacharias => B-PERSON
Elizabeth => B-PERSON
Solomon => B-PERSON
BEAR => O
WAS => O
WAY => O
STRIKE => O
WORSHIP => O
MURDER => O
KING => B-PERSON
Matthew => B-PERSON
Daughter => B-PERSON
Bartholomew => B-PERSON
Alphaeus => B-PERSON
Simon the Zealot => B-PERSON
BEFORE => O
Woe => O
Hades => B-LOCATION
Look => O
Jonah => B-PERSON
THIS => O
HOUSE => B-LOCATION
ROBBERS => B-PERSON
DEN => B-LOCATION
From => O
REJECTED => O
Caesar => B-PERSON
Whose => O
IF => O
DIES => O
UP => O
ABRAHAM => B-PERSON
ISAAC => B-PERSON
SOUL => O
MIND => O
AT => O
Well => O
Prophesy => O
JEWS => B-ORGANIZATION
Truly => O
CRYING => O
Gerasenes => B-GPE
HONOR => O
DIE => O
Galilean => B-ORGANIZATION
Council => O
Martha => B-PERSON
Pharisee => B-ORGANIZATION
Woman => B-PERSON
Word => O
Light => O
FATHER => B-PERSON
BROTHER => B-PERSON
RIGHT => O
Jesse => B-PERSON
BEHOLD => O
FORTH => O
EGYPT => B-GPE
Syria => B-GPE
Yours => O
OUR => O
Yes => O
Thomas => B-PERSON
MAN => B-PERSON
DAUGHTER => B-PERSON
WHOM => O
DAYS => B-TIME
HAS => O
Sir => B-PERSON
THINGS => O
Caesarea => B-GPE
BE => O
BECAME => O
BLESSED => O
SHEEP => O
HEAVEN => B-LOCATION
Whom => O
Praetorium => B-LOCATION
Skull => O
Joseph of Arimathea => B-PERSON
Simon of Cyrene => B-PERSON
Alexander => B-PERSON
Scripture => O
One => O
Savior => B-PERSON
Annas => B-PERSON
Stop => O
Samaritans => B-ORGANIZATION
Peace => O
Samaritan => B-ORGANIZATION
Lazarus => B-PERSON
Olivet => B-LOCATION
FEET => O
INTO => O
Jews => B-ORGANIZATION
Cana => B-GPE
Samaria => B-GPE
Tiberias => B-GPE
Greeks => B-ORGANIZATION
Didymus => B-PERSON
Romans => B-ORGANIZATION
SO => O
Roman => B-ORGANIZATION
Greek => B-ORGANIZATION
Men => B-PERSON
MADE => O
Asia => B-GPE
Pamphylia => B-GPE
Rome => B-GPE
EARTH => B-LOCATION
DECAY => O
Brethren => B-PERSON
Barnabas => B-PERSON
Ananias => B-PERSON
Stephen => B-PERSON
Antioch => B-GPE
AFTER => O
Men => B-PERSON
WHICH => O
Saul => B-PERSON
Caesarea => B-GPE
Damascus => B-GPE
Saul => B-PERSON
Joppa => B-GPE
Cornelius => B-PERSON
Joppa => B-GPE
Cyprus => B-GPE
Antioch => B-GPE
Mark => B-PERSON
Paul => B-PERSON
Perga => B-GPE
Iconium => B-GPE
Lystra => B-GPE
Silas => B-PERSON
Timothy => B-PERSON
Macedonia => B-GPE
Thessalonica => B-GPE
Jason => B-PERSON
Berea => B-GPE
Athens => B-GPE
Aquila => B-PERSON
Gallio => B-PERSON
Achaia => B-GPE
Ephesus => B-GPE
Artemis => B-PERSON
AMONG => O
YOUSHALL => O
EARS => O
RETURN => O
EVIL => O
CHIEF => O
COMES => O
FEAR => O
ARE => O
Brother => B-PERSON
Cyrene => B-GPE
Cilicia => B-GPE
THERE => O
PEOPLE => B-PERSON
Saul of Tarsus => B-PERSON
Italy => B-GPE
Alexandrian => B-ORGANIZATION
Pauls => B-PERSON
Felix => B-PERSON
Festus => B-PERSON
Agrippa => B-PERSON
Crete => B-GPE
WHOSE => O
BY => O
COME => O
COMMIT => O
LET => O
PUT => O
SAY => O
PRAISE => O
JACOB => B-PERSON
HAD => O
Abba => B-PERSON
Lords => B-PERSON
Cephas => B-PERSON
LET => O
MEN => B-PERSON
DAY => B-TIME
DID => O
Tarsus => B-GPE
Troas => B-GPE
Apollos => B-PERSON
Corinth => B-GPE
Gaius => B-PERSON
TIME => B-TIME
Greet => O
Titus => B-PERSON
SON => B-PERSON
NOR => O
VOICE => O
DEATH => O
ACCORDING => O
REASON => O
ABOUT => O
UNDER => O
HANDS => O
Holy => O
Holy of Holies => B-LOCATION
holy of holies => B-LOCATION
THEREFORE => O
ALSO => O
YEARS => B-TIME
BEGOTTEN => O
Philippi => B-GPE
Aristarchus => B-PERSON
LIVE => O
SAYS => O
WHILE => O
Galatia => B-GPE
Silvanus => B-PERSON
Tychicus => B-PERSON
Laodicea => B-GPE
Melchizedek => B-PERSON
HOPE => O
LEAVE => O
THE => O
tabernacle => B-LOCATION
time => B-TIME
Jesus the Nazarene => B-PERSON
GRANT => O
OF => O
Jordan River => B-LOCATION
Son of Man => B-PERSON
kingdom of heaven => B-LOCATION
you => B-PERSON
hometown => B-LOCATION
apostles => B-PERSON
dwelling place => B-LOCATION
BECAUSE => O
MAKE => O
PREPARE => O
UNTIL => O
KEEP => O
WOULD => O
OPEN => O
MAY => O
BUILDERS => B-PERSON
SAID => O
SIT => O
GO => O
TODAY => B-TIME
WHEN => O
NONE => O
WE => O
LIKE => O
DOWN => O
FOREVER => B-TIME
HARDEN => O
PATHS => O
ENEMIES => B-PERSON
HEARING => O
MOUTH => O
US => O
HEARTS => O
FOOTSTOOL => O
Lord Jesus Christ => B-PERSON
CALL => O
JUDAH => B-PERSON
HEARD => O
GREAT => O
BREAD => O
ANGELS => B-PERSON
CERTIFICATE => O
DIVORCE => O
AN => O
SACRIFICE => O
MANS => B-PERSON
SIGHT => O
SEND => O
MESSENGERAHEAD => O
REST => O
SPIRIT => B-PERSON
UNDERSTAND => O
SEEING => O
PERCEIVE => O
BECOME => O
BIRDS => O
THEAIR => O
ITS => O
RIGHTEOUS => O
TWO => O
FLESH => O
STEAL => O
WITNESS => O
ZION => O
COMING => O
EVEN => O
Christ Jesus => B-PERSON
apostle => B-PERSON
prophets => B-PERSON
Son of God => B-PERSON
world => B-LOCATION
RAISE => O
SUN => O
MOON => O
POWER => O
TOOK => O
BEEN => O
GAVE => O
Mary Magdalene => B-PERSON
MIGHT => O
WORM => O
FIRE => O
said => O
GOSPEL => O
PROCLAIM => O
BELIEVED => O
HATED => O
BLOOD => O
HOLY => O
LIFE => O
BRETHREN => O
JUDGE => O
OVER => O
KNOW => O
REMOVE => O
WHAT => O
THESE => O
TAKEN => O
DAVID => B-PERSON
SALVATION => O
KNOWN => O
PEACE => O
CREDITED => O
RIGHTEOUSNESS => O
SIN => O
COVENANT => O
EVERYONE => O
ENTER => O
OFFERINGS => O
